formpl.us 2019-03-06

# Terms & Privacy | Formplus - Online Form Builder & Data Collection Tool

## Privacy Policy

### What is this Privacy Policy?

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.formpl.us, and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.

This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations and requirements of users, the website and website owners. It will notify you of the following: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

2\. How this data is to be used

3\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

All information collected over Formplus forms is stored in the cloud storage of the form owner and Formplus for users who opt to store responses with us. This information is not accessed by Formplus except when account owner explicitly gives us permission to. This information is accessible from the cloud storage of the account owner and the assigned collaborators.

The forms hosted on Formplus and the content of each of the forms is the responsibility of the form owner. 

The form owner agrees to bear all liability for how the they handle such information and exempt Formplus from any liability on how the information collected through the Form is processed by the Form Owner.

Furthermore, the responsibility for satisfying the regulatory requirement for data collection and handling within each jurisdiction shall remain the responsibility of the Form Owner. Formplus recommends that each form owner create internal systems for satisfying the regulatory requirements within their different jurisdictions.

Furthermore, the form owners has full responsibility for proving that there exists satisfactory procedures compliant with the regulatory framework within their jurisdiction for the collection of sensitive data including but not limited to:

  * Personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs;
  * Trade union membership
  * Genetic data, biometric data processes solely to identify a human being
  * Heath-related data
  * Data concerning a person’s sex life or sexual orientation

In some events, and without playing any responsibility on Formplus, where there is reports of breach of the regulatory requirements for collecting and handling sensitive data or otherwise, Formplus will inform the form owner (customer) to remedy the breach. After informing the form owner, if the breach is still not remedied, Formplus may take any necessary steps to remedy the breach.

By logging in, you will give Formplus access to your email address and account information. This will only be used to setup your Formplus account and will not be shared with any third party. All your Formplus forms and data are tied to your email address.

Formplus is not responsible for any loss of data as a result of actions from the form owner or the assigned collaborators.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via support@formpl.us

  * Request what data we have on record about you.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

### Security

We take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of our users throughout their user experience. This website complies with all international law and requirements for user privacy. The website and all forms are SSL enabled 

Formplus receives payment through a third party payment processor, FastSpring. FastSpring addresses all PCI compliance issues, and securely processes sensitive data. Formplus is PCI compliant, and adheres to PCI DSS regulations. FastSpring’s e-commerce infrastructure is regularly monitored and credit card numbers are never stored. 

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. 

###  Orders

All orders are made from the Formplus website and subscriptions are renewed every month. You are automatically billed every month except if you opt out of the Formplus billing. 

Formplus also has a 100% refund policy, so that you would be refunded in cases where you do not wish to continue with the service, provided you are yet to receive 10% of your allotted responses (or up to 100 responses for the Professional plan) within 30 days of your payment. 

Our support agents would address all other questions or complaints. You can contact us directly at support@formpl.us or submit a ticket at support.formpl.us.

### Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. 

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time without notice, and all updates will be posted on this page.

**Our agents will address all questions regarding the privacy of your data. Please contact us directly at privacy@formpl.us**
